You never forget your first love.
Flipped is a romance, drama film directed by Rob Reiner.
When Juli meets Bryce in the second grade, she knows it's true love.
After spending six years trying to convince Bryce the same, she's
ready to give up - until he starts to reconsider.
Juli Baker, played by Madeline Carroll.
Bryce Loski, played by Callan McAuliffe.
Patsy Loski, played by Rebecca De Mornay.
Steven Loski, played by Anthony Edwards.
Chet Duncan, played by John Mahoney.
Trina Baker, played by Penelope Ann Miller.
Flipped is a 2010 American romantic comedy-drama film co-written and directed by Rob
Reiner, and based on Wendelin Van Draanen's 2001 novel of the same name.
Starring Callan McAuliffe, Madeline Carroll, Rebecca De Mornay, Anthony Edwards,
John Mahoney, Penelope Ann Miller, Aidan Quinn, and Kevin Weisman.
The film tells the story of Juli and Bryce, neighbors since the second grade who are never on the same page with their feelings until six
years later (just when she is about to give up) they both start to have feelings for each other, despite being total opposites.
Flipped was released in theaters in the United States
on August 6, 2010, by Warner Bros.
It garnered lukewarm reviews from critics and grossed
$4.3 million against a $14 million budget.
It has since garnered a greater appreciation for its realistic portrayal of teenagers and a wider viewership
via home video and streaming services, so much so that it is now considered a cult favorite.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, shyness,
family relationships, unrequited love, neighbor.
The tone is emotional.